Over the past two years youth unemployment has been on the rise
It currently represents just under 40% of all unemployment in Australia
Young graduates leaving University and finding it more and more difficult
2 into any form of creative industry
Now the Cummins stipulation is that
You can't get a job without experience
But you can't get a job to get the Experian
Now Maine wild
42% of small businesses fail
In 2003 to 2007
In the figures having improved much
Among the many reasons this is happening is
Consistent lack of quality in their branding marketing websites and Design
The kind
Of training that these graduates of just
Dispensary
Axios training for
Now what if there was an Enterprise